bigclicks.com 2005-04-11

# Homeland Alert System

**HOMELAND NETWORK PRIVACY POLICY**

**What Information Does Homeland Network Collect?**  
Homeland Network will provide information, services, and product offerings that are related to homeland security, data protection and other security related matters. To achieve this goal, Homeland Network will collect information so it can ascertain what your interests are, what your concerns are, what region of the country you live in and overall what makes you different from its millions of other unique users. While general access to the website does not require registration, access to certain areas, products and services will require you to become a member.

**Anonymous Information**  
Anonymous Information refers to data that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. For example, Homeland Network may collect information each time a visitor comes to a its website and network so that it can improve the overall quality of the visitor's online experience. Homeland Network may collect the visitor's IP address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from or aol.com), referral data (e.g., the Internet address of the last Web page visited by a user before clicking over to Homeland Network's website), and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). Homeland Network mal also collect search terms from its search services for internal reporting targeted advertising. Homeland Network collects this user information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement, and targeted advertising. You do not have to register with the Homeland Network's website before Homeland Network can collect this anonymous information. 

**Personally identifiable information**  
Personally identifiable information refers to data that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, e-mail and postal address, which may be collected in addition to the anonymous data described above. Homeland Network may collect personal information in the following ways: 

**Registration**  
When you register to gain access to certain parts of Homeland Network's website, Homeland Network's electronic (e-mail) newsletter, or access to certain services and/or products that Homeland Network offers, you will be asked to provide some or all of the following information: your name, postal address, ZIP Code, email address, birth date, gender, telephone number, occupation, marital status and other information. Please note that different products and services offered by Homeland Network require different levels of personally identifiable information, and, accordingly, depending on which product or service you are registering for, you will be asked to enter more or less personally identifiable information, than the ones listed above.   
Correspondence

If you contact Homeland Network, we may keep a record of that correspondence.   
Homeland Network reserves the right to collect certain information and store it in connection with your registration account. This information includes information about the different areas of the website that you visit as well as the time and frequency at which you visit them. This information also includes the content that you transmit or post on the Homeland Network website, including on message boards, forums and other such. 

**What organization is collecting the information?**  
When you register for a product or service, that information is generally collected and maintained solely by Homeland Network. However, at some times, data may be collected and/or maintained by any Homeland Network other than us, when you register or purchase third-party products and services. If you do not want to share your information with that Homeland Network, you can choose not to use that product or service. 

Be aware that Homeland Network sponsors and other advertisers have links on the Homeland Network website that take you to external sites. Some of these sites may collect personally identifiable information from you, and may use their advertisements to collect certain information from you, including but not limited to, cookies. Homeland Network's Privacy Policy does not cover any third-party data collection practices and Homeland Network does not assume any responsibility for any actions of third parties. 

**What are "cookies" and how does Homeland Network use them?**  
In addition to the personally identifiable information that Homeland Network actively collects when you register for a product or service, Homeland Network may also collect anonymous information passively using cookies. This technology plays an important role in making the Internet work.

A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a website to the hard drive of your computer so that the site administrator may identify your computer and passively track its activities on the Web site. This unique number identifies your Web browser to our computer system whenever you visit our website. A cookie will not allow a website to learn any personally identifiable information (such as your real name and address) that you have not otherwise disclosed. 

Cookies allow Homeland Network to automatically remember your Web browser when you visit our website. To help serve you better, Homeland Network generally uses cookies to: 

\- Allow us to deliver products and services more efficiently. By storing certain registration and preference information on cookies or associating cookies with registration, preference or profile information stored on our computers, we can deliver products and services that use such information more quickly and efficiently for more users.   
\- Measure statistics such as audience size and traffic patterns. This information is only collected in aggregate form and will not be linked to your personally identifiable information.  
\- Display advertisements. Cookies let us know whether a Web browser has seen a particular advertisement (so we can show you a variety of material) and count the number of advertisements displayed to a particular browser. We also use cookies to customize the advertising you see based on information that you provide when you register. Third-party advertising on Homeland Network's website may issue cookies when serving advertisements. 

The use of cookies is an industry standard, and they are currently used on most major websites. It is possible to adjust your Web browser preferences to alert you when a cookie is sent to your hard drive, or to refuse cookies altogether. However, please keep in mind that some of Homeland Network's products and/or services may not be accessible or may not function properly if this setting is selected.

**How does Homeland Network use the information it collects?**  
Any personally identifiable information you share with Homeland Network when registering for products and services is maintained and accessible only by Homeland Network unless specifically stated otherwise. Homeland Network requests information from its users so that users can enjoy customized experiences, including personalization services, interactive and person-specific communications and much more. It will also help Homeland Network better prepare future products and services based on your interests. 

The following are examples of how Homeland Network may use the information it collects: 

\- Homeland Network uses the information collected (both anonymous and personal) to personalize and enhance the content you see on the website, such as news, security reports, security updates, advertisements and more. In some cases, our products and services cannot work unless you have volunteered accurate information.

\- Homeland Network collects anonymous data and shares it with third-party advertisers in an aggregate form. We will disclose to those advertisers the numbers of users who have certain demographic characteristics and the number of those people who have seen and "clicked" on a particular display. We will also disclose to those advertisers the overall demographics available regarding who saw and "clicked" on their advertisement. In addition, we may disclose anonymous results from online surveys to third-party advertisers or to Homeland Network's product and service providers. No personally identifiable information will be disclosed as part of this process.

\- Homeland Network may use the aggregate data to perform statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our registered users and visitors, to measure user demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the website, and to analyze how and where best to use resources. Please note that we may share this aggregate information with third-party companies.

\- Homeland Network may collect an aggregate list of search terms from its search services. This information is collected anonymously and used primarily for the purposes of product development, monitoring, and improvement, as well as targeted advertising. Please note, however, that we may share this anonymous information with third-party companies.  
Homeland Network may use an individual registered user's data to "pre-populate" online forms that are displayed for the purpose of collecting additional individual data by Homeland Network, selected third-party sites, and/or sponsors and advertisers.

By providing Homeland Network with your personally identifiable information, you authorize Homeland Network to internally share that information with other companies in the Homeland Network's network, including companies that become part of this network in the future. Any Homeland Network in this network is authorized to share your personally identifiable information with any other Homeland Network of the network for the following purposes: to manage, administer, provide, expand and improve the existing products and services, and to offer new products and services; to adapt such products and services to your tastes and preferences; to send service updates to users; to send, by traditional and/or electronic means, technical, operational and commercial information relating to the products and services offered by the network or through any of the sites operated by the network, currently and in the future.

Homeland Network may disclose information about individual users to third parties who agree to provide services to Homeland Network. These third parties will provide a variety of services to Homeland Network, including, without limitation, processing and storing user information, helping to create new content and promotions for the Homeland Network, and sending or coordinating the sending of marketing communications that users have consented to receive. Homeland Network will disclose information about individual users to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies, or to other individuals or entities in response to subpoena, court order, or other legal process. In matters involving a danger to personal or public safety, Homeland Network may voluntarily provide information to appropriate governmental authorities. 

If Homeland Network is acquired by or merged with another Homeland Network, Homeland Network may transfer personally-identifiable information about you to that Homeland Network. 

**What is the opt-out policy for the Homeland Network?**  
There will be clear instructions to opt out of most email newsletters and direct mail communications within the communication itself. Upon registering to receive Homeland Network electronic newsletters, users will receive a confirmation e-mail that will verify that they have signed-up for the newsletter and give them the option of opting out. 

**What kinds of security procedures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your information?**  
Homeland Network has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. Homeland Network uses physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect any personally identifiable data stored on its computers. 

While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we take many precautions to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. 

You are ultimately responsible for the security of your ID names and passwords. Please take care when using and storing them. Homeland Network recommends that you do not divulge your password to anyone. You should log out of your browser at the end of each computer session to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence, especially if several people have access to your personal computer or you are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

**How does Homeland Network comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)?**  
The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998 provides safeguards to protect children who use the Internet by regulating the online collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. Because of these safeguards, children under 13 are not able to access or use all products and services of Homeland Network's. 

**What are the policies concerning software downloads?**  
Homeland Network may make certain software available for download. This software may be created by Homeland Network or by third party licensors. The software may be programmed to access our servers and/or third party servers in order for the software to operate and in order to check for program upgrades or enhancements. From time to time, new files may be added to your computer in order to upgrade the software or add new functionality to it. These changes may occur without notice to you. If at any time you wish to uninstall the software program, you may do so by following the instructions that acHomeland Network the software. Use of the software will be governed by a separate license agreement. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to: 

Prismatic Designs, Inc.  
1200 North Broom Street  
Wilmington, DE 19806  
302-269-3983   
866-301-4885

**Updates**  
Homeland Network will update this policy from time to time so please check back periodically. When such changes occur, you will see the word "Updated" next to the Privacy Policy link on the front page of the website.

Terms and Conditions :  Privacy Policy :  Contact us
